{
    "subject": "resource/Laurence_Marks_(British_writer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Believe_Nothing",
    "human_readable": "Laurence Marks is notable for his work 'Believe Nothing'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8769519925117493,
            "question": "Are there other works by Laurence Marks besides 'Believe Nothing'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7678208351135254,
            "question": "What genre does Laurence Marks' work 'Believe Nothing' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7663995027542114,
            "question": "What is the title of Laurence Marks' notable work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5873475670814514,
            "question": "What is Laurence Marks known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5130960941314697,
            "question": "Is Laurence Marks known for a specific philosophy or belief system?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38947704434394836,
            "question": "Who wrote 'Believe Nothing'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27940633893013,
            "question": "Who might be interested in reading 'Believe Nothing'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22045910358428955,
            "question": "What message does 'Believe Nothing' convey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1882469207048416,
            "question": "Which book or piece of writing by Laurence Marks emphasizes skepticism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18758068978786469,
            "question": "What impact has 'Believe Nothing' had on its readers?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Laurence Marks is notable for his work 'Believe Nothing'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8706_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which book or piece of writing by Laurence Marks emphasizes skepticism?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8706_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What message does 'Believe Nothing' convey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8706_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might be interested in reading 'Believe Nothing'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8706_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8706_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8706_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8706_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8706_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8706_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8706_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8706_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8706_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8706_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8706_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided documents mention Laurence Marks's career as a comedy writer and his collaborations with Maurice Gran. There is no mention of him being notable for \"Believe Nothing.\"  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention any work titled \"Believe Nothing\" by Laurence Marks. The context provided discusses his works such as the Frankie Howerd Show, Holding The Fort, and a new play called Love Me Do, but there is no reference to \"Believe Nothing.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information in the context provided to suggest that Laurence Marks is notable for his work 'Believe Nothing'.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Laurence Marks being notable for a work titled \"Believe Nothing\" within the provided context.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of \"Believe Nothing\" being associated with Laurence Marks in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of a work titled 'Believe Nothing' in the provided context. The information focuses on Marks and Gran's writing careers, particularly their work for Frankie Howerd, their sitcom \"Holding The Fort,\" and other plays and projects, but does not reference any piece named 'Believe Nothing.'",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}